Guide to the Business and Professional Women 1919-2010 bpw
Hartford Public Library, Hartford History Center, Publisher
Business and Professional Women1919-2010
bpw
16.5 linear feet (33 boxes)
Hartford Public Library, Hartford History Center
Hartford History Center, Hartford Public Library Hartford, Connecticut
Papers and records of the Hartford, Connecticut Business and Professional Women's Club.
Provenance
Not noted
Access Restrictions
See Hartford History Center’s Collection Use policy. Permission to publish from the Collection must be obtained in writing from curator of the Hartford History Center, and a copy of the published work may be requested by the Hartford History Center. The Hartford History Center reserves the right to refuse permission to publish, etc. to those who have not complied with its policies. Use of the collections will normally not be permitted for the purpose of promotion of commercial products and services or political campaigns. Hartford History Center at Hartford Public Library reserves the right to limit the number of photographic prints/captures and to restrict the use or reproduction of rare, fragile, or valuable objects.
Historical/Biographical Note
Founded in 1919, the Business and Professional Women's Club's purpose was "to establish a common meeting ground for business and professional women, to create good feeling among them, to furnish greater opportunity for advancement, to unite them into a thinking group for service." The organizational meeting was held in the auditorium of the Hartford YWCA. They maintained rooms at the Goodwin Building for a short period of time before purchasing a clubhouse on Myrtle Street. The clubhouse offered lodging and dining, which appealed to single, working women. Connecticut Mutual purchased the property in 1924, and the club rented space from then on. At its peak, the Business and Professional Women's club had 936 members. A fraction remained when the club disbanded in 2010. Club members were committed to community service and philanthropy. A project in 1924 involved partnering with Dixie Gas Co. The women sold ticket books that offered automotive gifts in exchange for gas purchases. In 1955 the club began a scholarship program for area high school seniors. Over $221,000 was awarded to both girls and boys, regardless of their intended major. Much of the money was raised through an annual fashion show.
Scope and Content Note
The records of the Business and Professional Women’s Club of Hartford contain meeting minutes, committee reports, newsletters, financial information, correspondence, newspaper clippings, photographs, membership rosters, and historical information. Also included are brochures, flyers, invitations, and programs from club events and records documenting the scholarships that the club presented to local students each year. The material ranges in date from 1919 to 2010, with an especially large amount of material from the 1980s. There are very few records from the 1930s and 1940s.
The first twenty-eight boxes of the collection are the general working records of the club and are arranged chronologically. Boxes 29 and 30 contain written accounts of the club’s history, research notes on the history of the club, information about archived club material, and other historical information. Some of this material is undated, but most of it appears to date from the 1980s. Box 30 also contains undated photographs and clippings. Boxes 31 and 32 contain miscellaneous photographs, while Box 33 contains flyers, brochures, programs and other ephemera.
Arrangement
Folders are arranged chronologically
The files are grouped into 1 series:
Inventory
Access Points
Subject Names:
Bailey, Francine; Baskerville, Ethel; Begansky, Dolores; Hosig, Terry; Potter, Mary E.; Ryan, Gertrude I.; Tyrol, Elizabeth H.; Yiznitsky, Nancy
Subject Topics:
By-laws; Clippings (Books, newspapers, etc.); Correspondence; Financial records; Fund raising; Scholarships
Subject Places:
Hartford (Conn.)
Document Types:
Minutes (administrative records); Photographs
Container List
[The following section contains a detailed listing of the materials in the collection.]
- Inventory
  - Meeting minutes, April~29,~1919-April~6, 1920 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Treasurer Reports, Miscellaneous, April~29,~1919-April~6, 1921 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Treasurer Reports, Miscellaneous, 1919-1924 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Annual Reports, Constitution, 1919-1920 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Minutes and reports, 1919-1920 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Copies of Meeting Minutes, April~1919-April~1920 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Hartford Times/Hartford Courant microfilm print-outs, 1919-1933 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Dixie Days publicity, ca.1920s (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Annual Reports, 1920-1921 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Membership List, 1920-1921 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - BPW Bulletin, Oct.~1921 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Minutes and reports, 1921 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Annual Reports, 1921-1922 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Program for BPW musical "Springtime", 1922 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Minutes and reports, 1922-1923 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Minutes and reports, 1923-1924 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Minutes and reports (copies), 1923-1924 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Minutes and reports, 1924 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - The Scribe (Official Bulletin of the Hartford BPW) - bound volume, 1921-1927 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Program for BPW musical, correspondence, resolutions, 1921-1944 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Photograph of BPW Clubhouse, ca.1920s (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Minutes and reports, June~1924-March~1925 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Minutes and reports (copies), 1924-1925 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Clippings - history of BPW clubhouses, 1924-1956 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Minutes and reports, April~1926-April~1927 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Program, 1931 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, 1935-1941 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Anniversary Dinner Programs, 1939; , 1949; , 1959, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Investment Statements, 1940-1948 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Treasurer's reports and budgets, 1951-1959 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Minutes, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Club By-laws, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Minuts and reports, 1954-1956 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Ethel Baskerville, publicity chairman, 1955-1956 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Minutes and reports, 1956-1957 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Elizabeth H. Tyrol, publicity chairman, 1956-1957 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Minutes and reports, April~1957-March~1958 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Gertrude I. Ryan, publicity chairman, 1958-1959 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Minutes and reports, newsletter, April~1958-April~1959 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Notes and correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Scholarship winners and clippings, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Minutes and reports, newsletter, April~1959-April~1960 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Mary E. Potter, publicity chairman, 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Annual reports and minutes, 1960-1961 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Minutes, reports, newsletters, other, April~1960-April~1961 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Alice V. Burns, publicity chairman, 1960-1961 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Minutes and reports, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Minutes and reports, 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Newsletter, other, 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence and reports, 1962-1968 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Scholarship awards and reports, 1962-1976; , 1984-1987 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Club By-laws, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Minutes, membership roster, newsletter, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Financial documents, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Minutes, reports, and newsletters, 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Board minutes, 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Investment statements, 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Minutes and reports, 1965-1966 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Newsletters, 1965-1966 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Annual meeting, annual reports, newsletters, 1966-1967 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Board minutes, 1966-1967 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Minutes and reports, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Annual reports, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Board minutes, annual meeting, annual reports, newsletters, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Minutes and reports, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Newsletter (copies), 1968 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Annual reports, membership roster, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Minutes and reports, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Minutes and reports, newsletter, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Clippings, 1960s-1970s (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, some with photocopies, 1970s; , undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Photocopies of BPW photographs D1-350, 1970s (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Photocopies of BPW photographs D351-680, 1970s-1990s (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Financial records, 1968-1970 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Investment book for scholarship account, 1968-1983 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Fiftieth Anniversary celebration, Oct.~9, 1969; , 1969 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Minutes and reports, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Newsletter, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Minutes, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Scholarship Information, 1969-1975 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Minutes and reports, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Newsletter, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Board minutes, annual meeting, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Annual reports, newsletter, other, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Annual reports, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Minutes and reports, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Newsletter, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Bills and receipts, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Bills and receipts for scholarships, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Minutes and annual reports, April~1971-March~1972 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Newsletter, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Board minutes and annual meeting, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Newsletter, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Annual reports, newsletter, other, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Board minutes and annual meeting, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Membership rosters, 1973-1975 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Minutes and reports, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Newsletter, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Annual reports, other, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Board minutes and annual meeting, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Charitable contributions and fundraisers, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Photographs, 1974-1979 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Newsletter, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Annual reports, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Treasurer's reports, scholarships, April~1975-March~1976 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Minutes and reports, April~1975-~April~1976 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Newsletter, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Board minutes, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Annual meeting minutes and annual reports, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - House committee, 1976-1978 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Fashions Galore, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Newsletter, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Annual reports, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Board minutes, annual meeting, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Newsletter, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Annual meeting minutes and annual reports, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Notes, plans, correspondence for annual luncheon/fashion show, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Board minutes, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Scholarship award winners, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Photographs, 1978; , 1985?; , undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Newsletter, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Suggested Procedures for Scholarship Chairman (1 of 2), Sept.~1979 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Suggested Procedures for Scholarship Chairman (2 of 2), Sept.~1979 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Minutes and reports, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Board minutes, annual reports, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence and notes, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Financial Information and vouchers, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Investment Committee annual reports, 1979-1988 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, menus for meetings, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Notes, plans, correspondence, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Minutes and reports, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Newsletter, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Annual reports, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Minutes, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Permits, bank statements, and receipts for raffles, 1980-1984 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Plans for board meetings, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Notes, plans, correspondence for annual luncheon/fashion show, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Minutes and reports, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - In Remembrance scrapbook, ca.1980 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Newsletter, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Program Committee records and correspondence, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Receipts, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Annual meeting minutes and annual reports, other, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Bank statements, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Board minutes, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Clippings and notes, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Community Service Committee records, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Fall Spectacular brochure and plans, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Scholarship awards, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Newsletter, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Board meeting and reception plans, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Notes, plans, correspondence for annual luncheon/fashion show, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Minutes and reports, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Annual reports, 1982-1983 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Membership roster, BPW Cook Book, 1982-1983 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Proposed ammendments to by-laws, 1982-1983 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Minutes, 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Committee records and correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Photographs, 1982?; , 1986-1988 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Membership Committee records, 1982-1988 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Membership rosters, 1982-1985 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Analysis of the Hartford BPW, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Connecticut Bank and Trust statements, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Minutes and reports, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Newsletter, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Clippings, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Annual reports, membership roster, 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Community Services Committee records, 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Receipts, deposit slips, vouchers, account informations, 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Minutes and reports, April~1983-April~1984 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Newsletter plans, 1983-1986 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, 1983-1989 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Newsletter, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Connecticut Bank and Trust statements, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Minutes and reports, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Annual reports, 1984-1985 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Charitable contributions, community service, 1984-1985 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Committee records, 1984-1985 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Deposit slips - general fund, April~1984-March~1985 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Photocopies of clippings, correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Vouchers- Bulletin, Community Services, and Fellowship Committees, 1984-1985 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Vouchers- Investment, Membership, Program, Publicity, and Scholarship Committees, undated (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Vouchers- House Committee, miscellaneous expenses, 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Vouchers- Ways and Means Committee, 1984-1986 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Ways and Means Committee reports and correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Minutes and reports, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Newsletter, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Annual reports, correspondence, other, 1985-1986 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Annual reports, membership roster, 1985-1986 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - General Fund bank statements, 1985-1986 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Investment account bank statements, 1985-1986 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Clippings, 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Program Committee records, 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Scholarship account bank statements, 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Minutes, 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Newsletter, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Minutes and reports, January--June~1986 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Minutes and reports, July-December~1986 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Photographs, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Treasurer's records, February-June~1986 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Treasurer's records, July-December~1986 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Annual reports, membership-roster, 1986-1987 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Minutes and reports, 1986-1987 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Meeting plans and vouchers, 1986-1988 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Minutes and reports, January-June~1987 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Minutes and reports, July-December~1987 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Newsletter, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Scholarship information, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Hartford Collection acquisitions, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Annual reports, membership directory, 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Meeting minutes, annual reports, 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Program Committee records, 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Soldiers and Sailors Arch rededication, 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Clippings, 1987-1989; , undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Minutes and reports, January-June~1988 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Minutes and reports, July-December~1988 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Newsletter, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Annual reports, calendar, 1988-1989 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - BPW Presidendt Francine Bailey correspondence and notes, 1988-1989 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Financial information, 1988-1989 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Scholarship Committee records (1 of 4), 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Scholarship Committee records (2 of 4), 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Scholarship Committee records (3 of 4) - correspondence, applications, bills, 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Scholarship Committee records (4 of 4) - history, previous recipients, 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, treasurer's reports, programs, 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Newsletter, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - BPW President Nancy Yiznitsky correspondence and notes, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Petra B. Shearer correspondence and notes, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Anniversary dinner photographs, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Photographs and negatives, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Minutes and reports, events, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - 70th and 75th Anniversary publicity and plans, 1989; , 1993 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Annual reports, 1989-1990 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Board minutes, annual reports, 1989-1990 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - BPW President Nancy Yiznitsky correspondence and notes, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Minutes and reports, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Newsletter, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Minutes, reports, and correspondence (1 of 2; some water damage), 1990-1991 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Minutes, reports, and correspondence (2 of 2; some water damage), 1990-1991 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Minutes, reports, and correspondence (1 of 2; copies), 1990-1991 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Minutes, reports, and correspondence (2 of 2; copies), 1990-1991 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Member of the Year Committee records, 1990-1991 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Minutes and reports, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Newsletter, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Flyers and programs for BPW events, 1991-1992 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Minutes, annual reports, membership directory, 1991-1992 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Photographs, 1991-1992 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, correspondence, other, 1991-1992 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Treasurer's reports, 1991-1992 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Newsletter, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Minutes, reports, and correspondence, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Tax forms, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Annual reports and membership directory, 1992-1993 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Scholarship Committee records, 1992-1993 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Scholarship Committee records - recipient information, 1992-1993 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Minutes and reports, other, 1992-1993 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Treasurer's reports, 1992-1993 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Member of the Year Committee records, 1992-1997 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Committee guidelines and forms, 1992-2002 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Newsletter, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Minutes and reports, events, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Membership directory, revised by-laws, 1993-1994 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Minutes and annual reports, 1993-1994 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Photographs and correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Ways and Means Committee recorda, 1993-1994 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Vouchers, 1993-1995 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Programs and brochures for BPW events, 1993-2006 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Minutes and reports, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Newsletter, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Scholarship Committee records, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Scholarship applications and acceptance forms, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Annual reports and membership directory, 1994-1995 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - BPW President Terry Hosig notes and correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Minutes and reports, 1994-1995 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Newsletter, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Minutes, reports, and receipts, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Annual reports, 1995-1996 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Photographs, 1995-1996 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - BPW President Dolores Begansky correspondence and records, 1995-1996 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Ways and Means Committee records, 1995-1996 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Income and expenses (1 of 2), 1996 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Income and expenses (2 of 2), 1996 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Minutes and reports, membership directory, correspondence, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Newsletter, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Annual reports and membership directory, 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Minutes, list of club officers, 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Community Services Committee records, 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Treasurer's Reports, 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence and forms- BPW material donated to Hartford Public Library, 1996-2004 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Minutes and reports, notes, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Newsletter, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Treasurer's Reports, 1997-1998 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Minutes, 1997-1998 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Community Services Committee records, 1997-1998 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Membership Committee records, 1997-1998 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence and reports, 1997-1998 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Annual reports and membership directory, 1997-1998 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, vouchers, brochures, 1997-1998 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Newsletter, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Member of the Year Committee records, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Minutes and reports, notes, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Scholarship awards dinner photographs, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Annual fall Fashion Show, Craft and Bake Sale brochures, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - ADHOC Committee Budget and Plans for 80th Anniversary Dinner, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Club Income, 1998-1999 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Fleet bank account statements, 1998-1999 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Annual Reports, membership directory, 1998-1999 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Archives Committee records, 1998-1999 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Club Officers, board of directors, 1998-1999 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Community Service Committee records, 1998-1999 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Member of the Year Committee records, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Minutes and reports, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Newsletter, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Photographs, 1999? (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Statement by John G. Rowland designating April 10, 1999 BPW Day (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - 80th Anniversary plans, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Community Service Committee records, 1999-2000 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Fellowship and Membership Committee records, 1999-2000 (Box 24, Folder 20)